Liam Devaney

Designer/Developer with a passion for UX & Project Management. Experienced in B2C/B2B ecommerce digital strategy, definition and refinement of KPIs and CRO. Regularly communicating with development, design and marketing teams while appreciating their difficulties and motivations.

4 Anvil Close, Southwater, RH13 9HD 07725973622 LiamDevaney@live.co.uk LiamDevaney.com

EXPERIENCE

Memset Ltd, Dunsfold — *User Experience Designer/Developer*

APR 2015 - PRESENT

- Development and reporting of Digital Strategy, Online Goals, KPIs and tactics
- Designing and implementing a change management process across the company
- Ensuring relevant stakeholders stay informed about changes
- Integrating third party systems including GetFeedback surveying, Salesforce CRM, Live Agent Chat, Pardot, Google Analytics, Google Tag manager
- Maintaining and developing company websites via a version controlled codebase
- Onboarding mid and senior level management
- Making intelligible data available to aid decision making
- Development and implementation of marketing strategy across media channels spanning CRM, web, email, PPC and social media
- Building marketing funnels and automation programs, finding improvements in the lead generation and acquisition process specific to business goals

Memset Ltd, Guildford — Web and Graphic Designer/Developer

JAN 2013 - APR 2015

Working with an experienced team of developers as the lead designer for digital media.

Binary Vision, Farringdon — Digital Production Assistant

JULY 2008 - SEPT 2009

Using AdobeCC and other technology to create new media for an array of digital projects.

EDUCATION

Portsmouth University — BSc Entertainment Technology

SEPT 2006 - JUNE 2010

St Marks, Hounslow — A-level and GCSE

MONTH 1996 - MONTH 2003

Advanced GNVQ in ICT, A-level Physics, 9 GCSE's A-C inc Math, English, Double Science.

PROJECTS

During my time at Memset I have managed various projects including, the release of both new and second generation products, the redesign of the basket and registration processes for public websites, as well as integrating a number of third party programs whilst championing user centered design and data driven decisions. I have enjoyed providing a single point of contact for stakeholders, and working with members of all departments towards these and other projects, as well as many smaller tasks.

Skills

Stakeholder Management
UX Design & Testing
Data Driven Decisions
User Centered Design
Change Management
KPI defining & reporting

Conversion Optimisation

PRINCE2 2017

TECHNICAL ABILITIES

Mac, Linux, Windows

HTML (A11y & Email), CSS & JavaScript

Google Analytics, AdWords, TagManager, Optimise, Piwik

SEO, PPC

Adobe Creative Cloud

Axure RP - Wireframing, Sitemaps, User Journeys

XMind - Navigation & Keyword mapping, Information Architecture

Content Marketing

Git, GitWeb, Gerrit, SVN

Salesforce, Pardot, Lead Generation

Django, Python